<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on tek256</title>
    <link>//tek256.com/tags/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on tek256</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 02:41:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//tek256.com/tags/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Optimization</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/workflow-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 02:41:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/workflow-optimization/</guid>
      <description>The last month or so has been a lot about workflow optimization for me. I&amp;rsquo;ve sort of made it an unscheduled tradition to go thru every few months and look at what fat I can trim out of my processes. The last month most of the &amp;ldquo;optimization&amp;rdquo; if you will, has been regarding my actual programming work and the things I&amp;rsquo;m working on. Currently I&amp;rsquo;m undergoing a pretty large refactor of Astera in order to make it a good bit more versatile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Jam</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/gamejam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 16:37:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/gamejam/</guid>
      <description>Hey, Since I didn&amp;rsquo;t take part in Ludum Dare 46 (I really didn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy the theme) I figure I still should do a jam of some sort. Now there&amp;rsquo;s plenty I could simply take part in and probably do decently well in. But I&amp;rsquo;m a bit old fashioned and don&amp;rsquo;t want to use Unity or Game Maker.
I&amp;rsquo;ve starting pulling a few things together and figured I could host my own game jam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>life changes</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/life-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/life-changes/</guid>
      <description>I’m gonna go ahead and preface this with I’m not looking for pity or any hand outs.
A few days ago I had a pretty negative life event happen. I’m still breathing and as healthy as I really can be. But my living situation &amp;amp; safety net got pulled out from under me. As a result, I’m lowering the time I allocate for my personal projects in order to look for work / contracts in the meantime to try and build up a safety net.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my bucket list</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/my-bucket-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 09:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/my-bucket-list/</guid>
      <description>One day I’m going to die. This is a universal truth for each and every one of us. The last few weeks before writing this have been rough for me. That’s why I’m writing this, as a message to my future self to recognize where I was and where I’ve gotten to. I encourage everyone to write a bucket list of their own.
Here are the current goals of mine, I won’t remove any, but I will add some if I start to run low.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>