<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on tek256</title>
    <link>//tek256.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on tek256</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 11:48:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//tek256.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 11:48:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/services/</guid>
      <description>Currently I&amp;rsquo;m offering a variety of different services:
 Commissioned Work Contracted Work Consulting Tutoring  Here are the different types of projects I&amp;rsquo;m open to working on! If you don&amp;rsquo;t see something on here that you&amp;rsquo;d like to ask about, definitely email me and ask!
 Game Development Game Engine Development Graphics / Rendering Development Enterprise Software General Software Development Front End Web Development Back End Web Development Full Stack Web Development  Here are some of the programming languages I&amp;rsquo;m most comfortable with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutoring</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/tutoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 13:49:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/tutoring/</guid>
      <description>Looking to get started in C? Maybe you want to learn programming from nothing! I offer tutoring &amp;amp; mentoring services open to everyone!
Tutoring Tutoring is where I&amp;rsquo;ll prepare materials beforehand and help teach &amp;amp; solve problems in real time over a voice / video call.
Here are the languages I can help teach:
 C C++ Java C# PHP HTML / CSS / Javascript  As well I can help tutor in Computer Science theory &amp;amp; fundamentals!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>Question Index:  How old are you?   Where are you from?   Are you going to school for Computer Science?   What&amp;#8217;s your day job?   What languages do you know?   What OS do you use?   What&amp;#8217;s your computer build?   What keyboard do you use?   What languages do you use for Game Development?   Why C?   How did you learn to write code?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/resume/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>