<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on tek256</title>
    <link>//tek256.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on tek256</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 02:41:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//tek256.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Optimization</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/workflow-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 02:41:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/workflow-optimization/</guid>
      <description>The last month or so has been a lot about workflow optimization for me. I&amp;rsquo;ve sort of made it an unscheduled tradition to go thru every few months and look at what fat I can trim out of my processes. The last month most of the &amp;ldquo;optimization&amp;rdquo; if you will, has been regarding my actual programming work and the things I&amp;rsquo;m working on. Currently I&amp;rsquo;m undergoing a pretty large refactor of Astera in order to make it a good bit more versatile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Jam</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/gamejam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 16:37:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/gamejam/</guid>
      <description>Hey, Since I didn&amp;rsquo;t take part in Ludum Dare 46 (I really didn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy the theme) I figure I still should do a jam of some sort. Now there&amp;rsquo;s plenty I could simply take part in and probably do decently well in. But I&amp;rsquo;m a bit old fashioned and don&amp;rsquo;t want to use Unity or Game Maker.
I&amp;rsquo;ve starting pulling a few things together and figured I could host my own game jam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>life changes</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/life-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/life-changes/</guid>
      <description>I’m gonna go ahead and preface this with I’m not looking for pity or any hand outs.
A few days ago I had a pretty negative life event happen. I’m still breathing and as healthy as I really can be. But my living situation &amp;amp; safety net got pulled out from under me. As a result, I’m lowering the time I allocate for my personal projects in order to look for work / contracts in the meantime to try and build up a safety net.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lost souls: about</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/lost-souls-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/lost-souls-about/</guid>
      <description>I figured enough has changed with Lost Souls over the last 8 months that I should probably write a little update post so people don’t have to wait for me to live stream to ask about it.
What is Lost Souls? Lost Souls is a Top Down (think original Zelda) 2D Action RPG. The goal is to make a game that’s fun to play but hard to master. It doesn’t include many frills, focuses mostly on the combat and pacing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>handmade seattle 2019</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/handmade-seattle-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/handmade-seattle-2019/</guid>
      <description>So this might be a little bit late, but here it is anyway. I finished editing most of the videos from Handmade Seattle 2019.
 There’s a whole playlist, but I won’t really bother putting it in here. I feel it’s probably pretty visible in the video description &amp;amp; ending.
Either way, let me know what you think about the editing! It’s been a few years since I’ve edited down a video of this size, usually I just make shorter meme videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my bucket list</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/my-bucket-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 09:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/my-bucket-list/</guid>
      <description>One day I’m going to die. This is a universal truth for each and every one of us. The last few weeks before writing this have been rough for me. That’s why I’m writing this, as a message to my future self to recognize where I was and where I’ve gotten to. I encourage everyone to write a bucket list of their own.
Here are the current goals of mine, I won’t remove any, but I will add some if I start to run low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pi zero: game console</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/raspberry-pi-zero-as-a-game-console/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 09:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/raspberry-pi-zero-as-a-game-console/</guid>
      <description>The above picture is the Raspberry Pi Zero W (Same size as the non-wireless) next to a standard US Quarter.
The following has been a side project of mine for a few months now. Mostly sitting idle while I do research on breaks.
Often times when people are told that someone is making a raspberry pi game console they think one of two things: Someone is building an emulation / retropie machine, or they don’t know what they’re talking about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lost souls: motivation</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/lost-souls-staying-motivated/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 03:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/lost-souls-staying-motivated/</guid>
      <description>Please don’t mistake this as a motivational post. I’m just kind of writing on the psychological aspects of this journey in game development that I’m observing in myself.
Motivation is an interesting thing. A lot of times today people are obsessed with “hustle” and bragging about it. It’s less of a brag and more of a norm in game development, especially seen in “crunch culture” or however you want to look at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lost souls: insanity</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/lost-souls-a-practice-in-insanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 07:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/lost-souls-a-practice-in-insanity/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure plenty of you are familiar with the general process of making a game. It’s a lot of back and forth with the things you’re using to create the game. Many ideas get left on the cutting room floor, many feel they should be there. At the end of the day, it’s common to feel like you’ve lost track of what you’re actually making. There is the rare project which seems to persevere in that front, but usually it just takes time to grind it into submission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>concept: lost souls</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/concept-lost-souls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 04:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/concept-lost-souls/</guid>
      <description>For the last few months I’ve been writing out and working on the details of a game I’ve been calling Lost Souls. The idea behind the story is that you’re trapped in purgatory and you don’t know how you got there. There are a few different levels of purgatory that you fight thru, similar to Dante’s Inferno.
All of the concept art and pixel art is being done by the wonderful Jackon LeTourneau, you can find him on twitter: whythecussnot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beyond the void: a brief history</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/beyond-the-void-a-brief-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 18:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/beyond-the-void-a-brief-history/</guid>
      <description>Beyond the Void is a dungeon crawler. It has randomly generated dungeons. You can play solo or online. In multiplayer you have 2 main options: You can crawl the dungeon with friends, or control the dungeon to stop them. If you haven’t played the demo already, I suggest you try it out. The demo is free and will always be free.
I’ve been working on the game in conceptual form for over 3 1/2 years now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>