<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thought on tek256</title>
    <link>//tek256.com/tags/thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thought on tek256</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 20:35:25 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//tek256.com/tags/thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>pursuit of a good life</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/pursuite-of-a-good-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 20:35:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/pursuite-of-a-good-life/</guid>
      <description>My brain likes to optimize things. It&amp;rsquo;s actually pretty good at it, unfortunately.
As a result, I spend a lot of time attempting to optimize my life. But you can only do so much. You can eat well, exercise, get proper rest, the list goes on. The struggle of existence is that it&amp;rsquo;s in flux at all times. One cannot effectively program their life, and expect it to stay that way forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>distractions</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 19:11:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/distractions/</guid>
      <description>Distractions are everywhere. As the years roll on, more and more effective distractions are created. They seem to be so wide reaching that being distracted is now considered a norm. Even hearing that someone is actively doing nothing is considered abnormal now. Boredom is often considered painful (not that it can&amp;rsquo;t be). But what seems to be a worse fate is doom scrolling and still bored. I see it all the time in myself and those around me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>an argument for old hardware</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/an-argument-for-old-hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 23:18:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/an-argument-for-old-hardware/</guid>
      <description>Throughout a lot of this writing, you can substitute old for “bad”. I use quotation marks around “bad” because hardware isn’t inherently bad or anything. It simply is often times slower relative to newer hardware. Knowing this, I offer this forewarning: In pursuit of acquiring better programming skills, don’t downgrade if avoidable. The idea of spending money to get older hardware I feel is a situational circumstance most often rewarded by specific projects, not everyday ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>being remembered</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/being-remembered/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 21:46:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/being-remembered/</guid>
      <description>How much of life do you actually remember? Which of these things do you remember? It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting concept that these memories are self history hosted within our own brains. Often they&amp;rsquo;re just not immediately accessible. If you think hard enough, what was it like when you were 3? How did you feel when you went to the first day of kindergarten? It&amp;rsquo;s all there, sometimes it just takes more time to retrieve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the portable developer</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/the-portable-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 04:20:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/the-portable-developer/</guid>
      <description>Imagine for a moment if you will, a developer who can work at any desk, with any computer, with any editor. What would that actually look like? How much time would it take for you to master each and every editor, how about operating systems? I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about this question a lot the last few days. As I transition into a chapter of my life where portability is becoming more of a factor, I&amp;rsquo;ve been asking these questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>programming principles</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/programming-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 13:44:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/programming-principles/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the last few weeks and months I’ve taken into great consideration what I actually need. Both personal and professionally, it seems like I’ve sort of had a decent layer of excess build up. By my own metrics I think I’m actually most the way “there” if you will. The last major step for me is moving from desktop to laptop. Regardless, I’m writing this to sort of set some of my personal preferences/metrics in stone for reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my bucket list</title>
      <link>//tek256.com/posts/my-bucket-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 09:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tek256.com/posts/my-bucket-list/</guid>
      <description>One day I’m going to die. This is a universal truth for each and every one of us. The last few weeks before writing this have been rough for me. That’s why I’m writing this, as a message to my future self to recognize where I was and where I’ve gotten to. I encourage everyone to write a bucket list of their own.
Here are the current goals of mine, I won’t remove any, but I will add some if I start to run low.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
